{
    "subject": "resource/WGAC-FM",
    "predicate": "property/owner",
    "object": "resource/Beasley_Broadcast_Group",
    "human_readable": "WGAC-FM is owned by Beasley Broadcast Group.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9193077683448792,
            "question": "Is Beasley Broadcast Group a radio station owner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8834275007247925,
            "question": "Who owns WGAC-FM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8692265152931213,
            "question": "Are there any other radio stations owned by Beasley Broadcast Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7616176605224609,
            "question": "What is the name of the company that owns WGAC-FM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7032996416091919,
            "question": "How many radio stations does Beasley Broadcast Group own?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6733225584030151,
            "question": "What type of business is Beasley Broadcast Group?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4746433198451996,
            "question": "What is the name of the radio station WGAC-FM?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33031320571899414,
            "question": "Name a company that owns a radio station."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23504559695720673,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a radio station owner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12432518601417542,
            "question": "What does it mean for a company to 'own' a radio station?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=WGAC-FM is owned by Beasley Broadcast Group.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6331_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a radio station owner?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6331_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a company that owns a radio station.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6331_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the radio station WGAC-FM?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6331_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6331_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is stated that \"WGAC-FM Technical Details:\" and then lists various details about the station, including its owner, which is \"Beasley Media Group Licenses, LLC\", a subsidiary of Beasley Broadcast Group, Inc."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports the statement that WGAC-FM is owned by Beasley Broadcast Group, as evidenced from the documents mentioning this ownership."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}